flyuia.com 2011-02-14

# Privacy policy - Ukraine International Airlines

As a valued Ukraine International Airlines customer, your personal privacy is very important to us. This page outlines our policy concerning personal information. By using the Ukraine International Airlines website, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time to take account of changing requirements such as changes in technology or legislation, and request that you refer back to this Policy frequently to become aware of any such revisions. In addition, we recommend that you review the privacy policy of any website accessed through the Ukraine International Airlines website as these sites may be subject to different privacy practices. Ukraine International Airlines is not responsible for these websites or for the information made available thereon. 

**How do I know my personal details are confidential and safe when I purchase flights or access my personal profile through the Ukraine International Airlines website?**

To ensure the security of your credit card information when you book flights through flyUIA.com, we use the latest Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. SSL is currently the preferred method to securely transfer credit card and other sensitive data over the Internet. If your browser supports SSL, please select the Secure Mode option when confirming your booking and your credit card and other personal details will be protected by this technology. 

If your browser does not support SSL, we recommend that you upgrade to the latest version of any browser to enhance the security of further transactions, otherwise the transmission of your personal data may not be protected and Ukraine International Airlines disclaims any responsibility in this regard 

Credit card sales are processed by RBS WorldPay Payment Systems, part of the Royal Bank of Scotland Group. 

**2\. What personal information does Ukraine International Airlines collect when I visit the Ukraine International Airlines website?**

We do not collect personal information about you when you browse the Ukraine International Airlines website. However, if you wish to book a flight using the site's interactive services, we will require you to complete the Booking Form and provide us with certain information which may include the following: 

Name  
Postal Address  
Credit/Debit Card number and expiration date  
Billing address  
Phone numbers  
E-mail address

**Personal Profile Number -Site Membership**

When you make an online booking with www.flyUIA.com you will be required to enter your personal information such as your Name, address, etc. Shortly after you have made your first booking we'll automatically send you an e-mail containing your Personal Profile Number and PIN. Next time you make a reservation on line you can enter your Personal Profile Number (and PIN) and the computer will recall information from your previous booking. You'll save time by not having to re-type your name, etc. Alternatively you can opt to make a booking as a Guest. 

We may also send site members information on services and special offers which we think they may find of interest. Site Members will also be asked to provide us with certain information by completing the User Profile. This information is optional and may include: 

Preferred / frequent destinations  
Home airport  
Opportunity to avail of e-mail notification of special offers  
Seat and meal preference  
Preferred class of service  
Age Group  
Credit/Debit card details 

**3\. How will Ukraine International Airlines use my personal information?**

We use your personal information to identify you as a customer, to process your booking, to verify credit or other charge card details, to manage your Panorama Club Account (if applicable) and to deliver relevant information to you in connection with your travel and any ancillary services which you may wish to avail of. Your information may also be used for immigration and customs control (see further below), security, administrative, and legal purposes. For these purposes, we may transmit your personal information to our own offices, authorised agents, other carriers and service providers, credit and charge card companies, data processing companies working on our behalf and to government and enforcement agencies. Some of these entities may be located outside the European Union. Your personal information and any records relating to your air travel will also be retained for audit functions. 

We may also use the personal information of Site Members to provide them with information which we think they may find of interest. This may include information about services, products, special offers and promotions offered by Ukraine International Airlines, other carriers and service providers. We may contact you by any means of communication for which you have given us contact details, including by post, e-mail, pop-up window, fax and telephone. However, you may choose not to receive such information by so indicating on the booking form or on the Site Membership Information form.

**4\. Cookies, web beacons and pixel tags and how they can benefit your website experience?**

Cookies are very small text files stored on your hard drive. They uniquely identify your computer and allow us to store profile information, improve website security and help us to customise your website experience. A unique user identity is created which ensures that you are not required to re-enter login details as you move throughout the website. Time spent navigating the site is kept to a minimum. As is described in more detail below, they may also be used to assist us in making our website and our emails work more efficiently as well as to provide us with business and marketing information. For more detailed information on cookies, visit www.allaboutcookies.org. 

**(a) Technology used during your web visit**

We contract with online partners to help manage and optimize our internet business and communications and to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. To do this, we use cookies provided by our online partners on this site. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things such as what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although our online partner logs the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. 

If you do not want to help us learn how to improve our site, products, offers and marketing strategy, you can "opt-out" of this website analysis tool. How you do this will depend upon the internet browser you use (for example, Internet Explorer 5, Netscape 4 or Opera etc). Please refer to the relevant internet browser manufacturer's website where you should be able to receive all the information required. 

**(b) Technology used in our e-mails**

In addition, we may use e-mail delivery and marketing companies to send e-mails that you have consented to receive. Pixel tags and cookies may be used in those e-mails and at our website to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our website. 

The following is a list of all the cookies that Ukraine International Airlines or its third party contractors may use for this purpose:

"Email Opening Sensing": In order to understand how our readers interact with the emails and the content that we send, we may use pixels in the text in order to understand who has opened the emails that they have been sent. 

"Message Format Sensing": In order to provide our content in the most interesting way, we may also use pixels to learn whether you can receive emails in text or html form. 

"Click-Through Sensing": If you click on a link in the email, we may set a cookie on your browser. 

"Response Analysis": If you click on a link in the email, we may set a cookie on your browser. If you visit our website as a result of clicking on a link, we are able to understand how you interact with the pages of our website through the combination of the cookie and pixels set on the pages of our website. This enables us to understand what interested you in our emails and what did not, and what interests you about our website and what does not. We can then try to send you more interesting information in the future. Please note that this information is for our use only - we do not disclose or share this information with any third parties. If you do not wish this to happen, you can change the cookie settings in your browser. 

**5\. Is it easy to update and alter my personal information?**

You may access and update the information which we hold about you as a Panorama Club logging in and accessing the relevant page in the Panorama Club section of the website. If you wish to update your Personal Profile please email changes to bookinghelp@ps.kiev.ua quoting your Personal Profile Number. 

**6\. Contact us**

If you have any other concerns, suggestions or questions about any issues relating to privacy on the Ukraine International Airlines web site, please contact us via e-mail, bookinghelp@ps.kiev.ua

Issued: 011006 ENG
